Contact

119, room no 9, 21 st cross 16 th main road BTM Layout 2nd stage Bangalore 560076.
9794664175 (Home)
abhishek.abvp.as@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/abhisheksingh-16bb53143 (LinkedIn) www.iamabhishek.me/ (Portfolio) blogs.iamabhishek.me/ (Blog)

Top Skills

Linux

High Availability
Redhat certified engineer

Certifications

Red Hat Certified Engineer (RHCE)
Red Hat Certified System
Administrator (RHCSA)

Abhishek Singh

Not so Devops Engineer at SKILLEDANSWERS INFOSOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED

Bengaluru

Summary

I am a highly skilled Linux Engineer with experience in large scale enterprise systems and networks, virtualization environments and software development. I thrive in an environment where teamwork is important, but can work on my own projects. My interests include scripting (Python/Perl/Linux), web development (Linux System Administration/MySQL/JS) and cloud technologies (AWS). Other areas of interest include network infrastructure (NOC) and security (IDS/IPS)

Experience

SKILLEDANSWERS INFOSOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED 10 months

Not so Devops Engineer July 2021 - Present (4 months) India

Linux Engineer
January 2021 - August 2021 (8 months)

Netzary Infodynamics Linux Engineer November 2019 - January 2021 (1 year 3 months) Bengaluru Area, India

Education

IANT

Diploma, Cyber/Computer Forensics and Counterterrorism · (2016 - 2018)